Guide to the Women Writing Women's Lives Records TAM.316
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Oral History Interviews, 2006-2009; 2 Linear Feet in one manuscript box, one cassette box, and two CD boxes; 3 audiocassettes; 4 VHS; 16 CDs; 7.7 Gigabytes in 47 computer files
  Series IV: Oral History Interviews (2006-2009) contains interviews with members of the group Women Writing Women's Lives. These interviews were conducted by other WWWL members and Tamiment director Michael Nash between 2006 and 2009. They discuss topics such as the founding of the writing seminar, and the ways in which participation in Women Writing Women's Lives shaped these authors' careers as biographers. The collection also contains several notes and biographical documents compiled in preparation for these interviews. Electronic Records include digital audio files of each interview.
  - Bair, Diedre, January 12 - April 30, 2009; cuid44614
    - Biographical notes, April 30, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Interview transcript, January 12, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Original CD (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_13)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_1
  - Bernikow, Louise, April 7, 2006; cuid44416
    - Interview transcript (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Original audiocassette, cuid44419 (Box Shared Tamiment 106, Audiocassette cuid44419)
    - Original CDs (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_1, TW_TAM_316_2, TW_TAM_316_3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_2
  - Brownstein, Rachel, May 28, 2009; cuid44417
    - Interview transcript (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Original audiocassette, cuid44421 (Box Shared Tamiment 106, Audiocassette cuid44421)
    - Preservation copy (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_16)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_3
  - Chase, Norah, May 30, 2008 - April 2, 2009; cuid44615
    - First Interview -- Transcript and biographical materials, May 30, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - First Interview -- Original CD, May 30, 2008 (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_9)
    - First Interview -- Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_4
    - Second Interview -- Original CDs, April 2, 2009 (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_10, TW_TAM_316_11)
    - Second Interview -- Preservation copy, April 2, 2009 (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_12)
    - Second Interview -- Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_5
  - Cook, Blanche Weisan, October 2, 2007; cuid44616
    - Interview transcript (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Original CD (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_6
  - DeSalvo, Louise, November 20, 2008; cuid44418
    - Interview transcript (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Original audiocassette, cuid44420 (Box Shared Tamiment 106, Audiocassette cuid44420)
    - Original CD (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_14)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_7
  - Moore, Honor, October 19, 2007; cuid44617
    - Interview transcript (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Original CD (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_8
  - Munker, Dona, June 18, 2007; cuid44618
    - Interview transcript (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Original CDs (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_6, TW_TAM_316_7)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_9
  - Painter, Nell, April 21, 2009; cuid44619
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    This interview's recording has distorted audio.
    - Interview transcript, April 21, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Preservation copy (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_15)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_10
  - Shapiro, Sue, 2007-2008; cuid44620
    - Interview transcript, November 6, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Biographical notes, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Original CD (Box Shared Tamiment 199, Cd TW_TAM_316_8)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_316_ER_11